dominionenergy.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy | Dominion Energy

## Protecting Your Privacy

At Dominion Energy, privacy is an important part of how we do business. We're committed to protecting your personal data while providing safe, reliable and affordable services. This Privacy Policy explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used via the Dominion Energy website.

## Information We Collect

To promote the most efficient use of our products and services and to provide easy access to our website, Dominion Energy collects information about its customers both directly and through the use of cookies stored on customers' computers.

Customers provide information when they open an account, participate in a Dominion Energy program, contact us via the Web or use one of our services.

Examples of information you may provide to us while using our site include: 

  * Contact information such as customer name, mailing address, phone and email address
  * Billing information related to your financial relationship with us, including your payment history and account number
  * Social Security number

When you visit our website, our servers may create cookies on servers and computers, making it more convenient for you to use the website by verifying when you travel from page to page. The data we collect on website usage from cookies is maintained securely and is not tied to your personal information. We do not sell or transfer the data we obtain from cookies, and we only use it in aggregate form or to contact you to offer programs and/or services you may be interested in. If you object to this, please consult your browser’s documentation for information on erasing or blocking cookies. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some areas of our website could be limited.

Personal information identifies you specifically. By providing personal information, you are agreeing to permit us to access, store and use the information as described in this document.

## How Dominion Energy Uses the Information We Collect

Any information we gather, whether voluntarily provided by you or automatically collected, may be used to provide requested services, support our business functions and for marketing purposes, in accordance with applicable laws and restrictions. For example, we may use your information to:

  * Provide customer service 
  * Respond to your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests 
  * Answer your questions
  * Register and service your account 
  * Improve our services
  * Notify you about services and changes that may affect you
  * Conduct market research
  * Share important information (for example, during a major storm)

Notwithstanding any other statements or representations here or elsewhere on our website, we reserve our right to disclose any information in our possession if we are required to do so by law, as requested by our regulatory agencies, in connection with the sale of all or a portion of our businesses, or if we believe, in good faith, that such a disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, defend our rights or property, or to respond to an emergency situation.

## How Dominion Energy Protects Your Personal Information

We treat all personally-identifying information of our customers as confidential. Dominion Energy does not sell your personal information, nor does Dominion Energy provide such information to third parties for the purpose of marketing products or services unrelated to Dominion Energy's services. Dominion Energy does not disclose your information to third parties for any purpose, except under strict contracts involving customer service, collections or the enhancement of our customer programs.

Dominion Energy is strongly committed to protecting the privacy, security and integrity of your information. Dominion Energy uses industry-standard practices to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include, but are not limited to, firewalls, intrusion monitoring, and technology to encrypt and protect certain sensitive transmissions of information. However, no security system is fail-safe, and Dominion Energy cannot guarantee the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. You should protect the confidentiality of your information such as your customer account number, email address and password.

Dominion Energy will not intentionally disclose your password to a third party; however, you are also responsible for maintaining the privacy and security of your password. We strongly urge you to take precautions to guard the confidentiality of your user name and password. We advise you to not share your user name and password with third party services or use your password with any other Website. Passwords are your first line of defense against unauthorized access to your account. If your password is compromised, your information can be misused. If you believe your password has been compromised in any way, please contact us.

## Other Information

For the convenience of our users, in some cases, our website links to third party sites that collect personal information by and for other parties. In these cases, you will leave Dominion Energy’s website, and the personal information you provide on those sites will be governed by the privacy policy of that site. Dominion Energy does not assume responsibility for the actions of other parties. When using a link to a non-Dominion Energy website, we recommend that you investigate the privacy practices and policies of such external site. Any use of external links is at the sole discretion of the user.

From time to time, we may change our privacy policy and will make reasonable efforts to publish such changes.

If you are concerned about the information you have provided to us, or would like to review, update or delete that information, please contact us. Please allow us up to ten business days for the change to take effect. 

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Dominion Energy reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you here prior to the changes taking effect, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. When an update is made, the date at the bottom of this page changes to reflect the date new content was posted. Use of our website after the posting of a revised privacy policy constitutes your agreement with the revised policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

_Last Updated 05/11/2017_
